<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="items_label">Pilih Kategori</string>
    <string name="google_map_api_key">

     AIzaSyBXKI8yvEg3meRhpgPYcJV8_Hq7_Dowf48
    </string>
    <string name="satoru">Satoru believes he is the strongest person in existence, and he is most likely correct. He confidently states that he could defeat Sukuna even if he regained all his fingers, and that is not just an empty boast. He has an immense amount of cursed energy, and never seems to get tired. His Limitless Technique is completely overpowered, as it not only allows him to essentially avoid all damage, but also allows him to create powerful singularities that can destroy anything they touch. Satoru is easily the most powerful character in the series, and arguably one of the strongest in any anime.</string>
    <string name="sukuna">The undisputed King of Curses, Sukuna is so powerful that a single one of his fingers is enough to create a special grade Curse. He easily defeated the Finger Bearer in the juvenile detention center, and can literally tear opponents apart with his Dismantle Technique, such as when he slashed Mahito after the Curse tried too many times to touch Sukunas soul.
        His Domain Expansion: Malevolent Shrine, allows him to attack anything within 200 meters at will, and if thats not enough, he is incredibly cunning and patient. Sukuna is willing to wait for the perfect chance to strike, and once he does, he hardly ever misses.</string>
    <string name="yuta">The hero of Jujutsu Kaisen 0, Yuta Okkotsu might be young, but he easily earns a high rank among Jujutsu Kaisen strongest characters. His initial strength comes from the raw power of the cursed spirit of his dead best friend, Rika, who jealously watches over him. Though he isnt sure how to control Rika s power at first, once the two get in synch, they re strong enough to take on and beat the special-grade sorcerer Geto. Though fans of the anime havent seen much of Yuta since he went on a training mission at the end of Jujutsu Kaisen 0, his return could very well herald the next sorcerer on Gojo`s level.</string>
    <string name="toji">One of the few non-curse users among Jujutsu Kaisen`s strongest characters, Megumi`s father is an absolutely monstrous fighter who should not be underestimated. Taking on a jujutsu sorcerer like Geto and winning without much hassle is a tall order. Effortlessly beating Gojo should basically be impossible. What makes Fushiguro so intimidating is his raw strength and his in-depth knowledge of the sorcerer community. His bloodlust and ability to take on even the strongest sorcerers rightly earned him the title Sorcerer Killer. Though a handful of sorcerers have surpassed Toji since his time, in his prime, he was close to unstoppable.</string>
    <string name="geto">A former hero turned villain, Geto is one of four special-grade sorcerers recognized by Jujutsu High. The former heros true claim to fame is his unreasonable reserve of cursed energy which lets him manipulate and control thousands of powerful cursed spirits without much effort. Geto can than combine those curses into the unreasonably powerful Maximum Uzumaki attack. Even if he didn`t have an abundant supply of cursed energy, Geto`s mastery of hand-to-hand combat puts him among Jujutsu Kaisen`s strongest martial artists. It`s a testament to the absurd power levels reached by some of Jujutsu Kaisen`s strongest characters that Geto isn`t the series` most powerful character.</string>
</resources>